Guide to the H.M. Chester Photograph Collection 1892-1910, undated PR 131
@ 2011 New-York Historical Society
- New York
  - Rochester
    - Genesee Falls, 1907 June (Box 7, Folder 389)
    - Genesee River - In canoe, 1907 June (Box 7, Folder 390)
    - The Gorge - Genesee River, undated (Box 7, Folder 391)
    - Fountain in Jones Park, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 392)
    - Lake Avenue, undated (Box 7, Folder 393)
    - Lake Avenue - Baptist Church, undated (Box 7, Folder 394-395)
    - Man of War, undated (Box 7, Folder 396)
    - Park in Rochester [Genesee Valley Park?], undated (Box 7, Folder 397)
    - Rochester, undated (Box 7, Folder 398)
- Oregon
  - Portland – Lewis & Clark Centennial American Pacific Exposition (1905)
    - Columbia River, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 399-400)
    - Exposition Grounds, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 401)
    - Forestry Building, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 402-403)
    - U.S. Government Building, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 404)
- Pennsylvania
  - Gettysburg
    - John Burns Monument, undated (Box 7, Folder 405)
    - Devil's Den, undated (Box 7, Folder 406)
    - [First Massachusetts Infantry] Monument, undated (Box 7, Folder 407)
    - High Water Mark, undated (Box 7, Folder 408)
    - Little Round Top - 91st Penn. Regiment Monument, undated (Box 7, Folder 409)
    - Little Round Top - View of the Cannons, undated (Box 7, Folder 410)
    - Major General John Fulton Reynolds Monument, undated (Box 7, Folder 411)
    - Soldiers National Monument, undated (Box 7, Folder 412)
- Rhode Island
  - Watch Hill
    - Watch Hill [water view], undated (Box 7, Folder 413a)
  - Westerly
    - Armory Hall, undated (Box 7, Folder 413b)
    - High & Canal Street, undated (Box 7, Folder 413c)
- Utah
  - Salt Lake City
    - Amelia's Place, undated (Box 7, Folder 414)
    - The Bee Hive, undated (Box 7, Folder 415-416)
    - City & County Building, undated (Box 7, Folder 417)
    - Eagle Gate, undated (Box 7, Folder 418-419)
    - The Lion House, undated (Box 7, Folder 420)
    - Mormon Temple, undated (Box 7, Folder 421)
    - Remains of the Old Wall, undated (Box 7, Folder 422)
    - Salt Air [Pavilion], undated (Box 7, Folder 423)
    - Tabernacle, undated (Box 7, Folder 424)
    - Brigham Young's Grave, undated (Box 7, Folder 425)
    - Statue of Brigham Young, undated (Box 7, Folder 426-427)
- Virginia
  - Arlington
    - Robert E. Lee Mansion, undated (Box 7, Folder 428)
- Washington
  - Seattle – Alaska-Yukon-Pacific Exposition (1909)
    - Arch of Welcome, 1909 (Box 7, Folder 429)
    - Chinese Parade, 1909 (Box 7, Folder 430)
    - Entrance to the Exposition Grounds, 1909 (Box 8, Folder 431)
    - Foreign Building, 1909 (Box 8, Folder 432)
    - Hawaii Building, 1909 (Box 8, Folder 433)
    - Igorrote Indians, 1909 (Box 8, Folder 434-436)
    - Oriental Building, 1909 (Box 8, Folder 437)
    - Sight Seeing Auto - Volunteer Park, 1909 (Box 8, Folder 438-439)
    - Totem Pole - Pioneer Square, 1909 (Box 8, Folder 440)
    - U.S. Government Building, 1909 (Box 8, Folder 441-442)
    - Vancouver Arch, 1909 (Box 8, Folder 443)
- Wyoming, Idaho & Montana
  - Yellowstone National Park
    - Buildings – Mammoth Hot Springs Hotel, undated (Box 8, Folder 444)
    - Buildings – Mammoth Hot Springs Hotel - Second stage, undated (Box 8, Folder 445)
    - Buildings – Old Faithful Inn, undated (Box 8, Folder 446)
    - Buildings – Old Faithful Inn - Bears, undated (Box 8, Folder 447-449)
    - Geysers – Giant Geyser, undated (Box 8, Folder 450)
    - Geysers – The Grand Geyser, undated (Box 8, Folder 451)
    - Geysers – Old Faithful Geyser, undated (Box 8, Folder 452-453)
    - Geysers – The Riverside Geyser, undated (Box 8, Folder 454)
    - Geysers – Turban Geyser, undated (Box 8, Folder 455)
    - Geysers – Upper Geyser Basin, Tourists at, undated (Box 8, Folder 456-457)
    - Water Features – The Devil's Bathtub, undated (Box 8, Folder 458)
    - Water Features – Firehole River, undated (Box 8, Folder 459)
    - Water Features – Grand Canyon Bridge over Yellowstone River, undated (Box 8, Folder 460)
    - Water Features – Yellowstone Canyon and River, undated (Box 8, Folder 461-464)
    - Water Features – Yellowstone Canyon & Upper Falls, undated (Box 8, Folder 465)
    - Water Features –, undated
    - Water Features – Yellowstone Lake, undated (Box 8, Folder 466)
    - Water Features – Yellowstone Lake & Teton Mountains, undated (Box 8, Folder 467-468)
    - Water Features – (Large) Yellowstone Falls, undated (Box 8, Folder 469)
    - Miscellaneous – Bear at Yellowstone, undated (Box 8, Folder 470-471)
    - Miscellaneous – The Grotto, undated (Box 8, Folder 472)
    - Miscellaneous – Hymen Terrace, undated (Box 8, Folder 473)
    - Miscellaneous – Jupiter Terrace, undated (Box 8, Folder 474)
    - Miscellaneous – Jupiter Terrace Cascades, undated (Box 8, Folder 475)
    - Miscellaneous – Liberty Cap, undated (Box 8, Folder 476-477)
    - Miscellaneous – Six horse stage at Gardner Entrance, undated (Box 8, Folder 478)
    - Miscellaneous – Terrace, undated (Box 8, Folder 479)
- Mexico
  - Tijuana?
    - Boundary Monument - between U.S. and Mexico, undated (Box 8, Folder 480)
    - The City of Tia Junta [Tijuana?], undated (Box 8, Folder 481)
    - Old Mission - Tia Junta [Tijuana?], undated (Box 8, Folder 482)
    - One foot in Mexico - one foot in U.S. [man by border monument], undated (Box 8, Folder 483)
  - Miscelleneous
    - Sweet Water Reservoir & Dam showing mountains in Old Mexico, undated (Box 8, Folder 484)
- Miscellaneous
  - Animals
    - Cats, undated (Box 8, Folder 485-488)
    - Dog, undated (Box 8, Folder 489)
    - Elephant, undated (Box 8, Folder 490)
    - Lion, undated (Box 8, Folder 491)
    - Ostrich, undated (Box 8, Folder 492)
    - Tiger, undated (Box 8, Folder 493)
  - Buildings
    - Unidentified Buildings, undated (Box 9, Folder 494-500)
  - Flower Shows
    - Dahlia Show, 1907 (Box 9, Folder 501-504)
    - Chrysanthemum Show, 1907 (Box 9, Folder 505-508)
  - Landscapes
    - Unidentified landscapes, undated (Box 9, Folder 509-521)
  - People
    - Arabs - Buffalo Bill, undated (Box 9, Folder 522-523)
    - [H.M. Chester beside tree], undated (Box 9, Folder 524)
    - Georgie & Dog on Table, undated (Box 9, Folder 525)
    - [W.E. McCarthy?], undated (Box 9, Folder 526)
    - Nellie's Baby, undated (Box 9, Folder 527)
    - Herbie & Gladys Simon, undated (Box 9, Folder 528)
    - Unidentified people, undated (Box 9, Folder 529-531)
  - Ships
    - Blake under way, undated (Box 9, Folder 532)
    - Columbia, undated (Box 9, Folder 533)
    - Mianto?, undated (Box 9, Folder 534)
    - Miantomah, undated (Box 9, Folder 535)
    - New De Julia, undated (Box 9, Folder 536)
    - Nina, undated (Box 9, Folder 537)
    - The Pilgrims boat, undated (Box 9, Folder 538)
    - Pinta, undated (Box 9, Folder 539)
    - Sant Maria, undated (Box 9, Folder 540)
    - Steamer Ella, undated (Box 9, Folder 541)
    - Vicking, undated (Box 9, Folder 542-545)
    - Unidentified ships, undated (Box 9, Folder 546-549)
      See also: 564, Box 9
  - Street scenes
    - Unidentified street scenes, undated (Box 9, Folder 550-552)
- Oversize
  - North Stonington, Connecticut
    - Mr. H.M. Chester on the farm, undated (Box 10, Folder 553-554)
    - Mrs. H.M. Chester - view at North Stonington farm, undated (Box 10, Folder 555)
    - Cow on the farm, undated (Box 10, Folder 556)
    - View at North Stonington Farm, undated (Box 10, Folder 557-558)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Our Dick - 17 years old weighed 25 lbs. [cat], undated (Box 10, Folder 559)
    - W.E. McCarthy, undated (Box 10, Folder 560-561)
- Photographic Prints
  - Contact print from 36, Log Cabin - Adams Street, Los Angeles, California, undated (Box 10, Folder 562)
  - Contact print from 169b, Mrs. H.M. Chester (Emma) at Grizzly Giant, Yosemite National Park, California, undated (Box 10, Folder 563)
  - Contact print from 549, Unidentified ship, undated (Box 10, Folder 564)